<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
	    <template id="web.external_layout_standard">
			<div t-attf-class="header o_company_#{company.id}_layout">
				<div class="row">
					<div class="col-3 mb4">
					    <img t-if="company.logo" t-att-src="image_data_uri(company.logo)" style="max-height:105px;margin:0px;padding:0px;" alt="Logo"/>
					</div>
					<div t-if="doc" style="width:auto;margin-left:680px;margin-top:5px;">
					    <div>Sale Order: <span t-field="doc.name"/></div>
                        <div>Order Date: <span t-esc="doc.date_order.strftime('%m/%d/%Y')"/></div>
						<div>Showroom: <span t-field="doc.team_id"/></div>
                        <div>Salesperson: <span t-field="doc.user_id"/></div>
					</div>
				</div>
			</div>
			<div t-attf-class="article o_report_layout_standard o_company_#{company.id}_layout" t-att-data-oe-model="o and o._name" t-att-data-oe-id="o and o.id" t-att-data-oe-lang="o and o.env.context.get('lang')">
				<t t-call="web.address_layout"/>
				<t t-raw="0"/>
			</div>

			<div t-attf-class="footer o_standard_footer o_company_#{company.id}_layout" style="font-size:8px;">
					<div t-field="company.report_footer" class="text-muted"/>
					<div class="text-muted">The Terms and Conditions of Sale, including arbitration of disputes, are printed on the next page. Please read them carefully. Seller's receipt of
	a 50% deposit constitutes Buyer's acknowledgement of this order and agreement to all terms and conditions of Sale. Unless we are notified of any errors in
	this order within (10) days of the Order Date, this order will stand as final.</div>
					<div t-if="report_type == 'pdf'" class="text-muted">
						Page: <span class="page"/> / <span class="topage"/>
					</div>
			</div> 
                <div class="row col-xs-12" style="font-size:9pt;page-break-before:always;">
                    <div style="margin-left:5px;font-size:9pt;">Revised: 01-16-2015</div>
					<div style="margin-left:350px;"> TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SALE</div>
<p>1. Scope of Agreement. These Terms and Conditions of Sale ("Terms") 
are a legally binding agreement between you and Dennis &amp; Leen and/or Formations and govern your purchase of any 
products from either company. These Terms apply to all merchandise sold to all customers. These terms may not be
 altered in any manner without our prior consent. Our receipt of a fifty percent (50%) deposit on your order constitutes 
 your consent and agreement to these Terms.</p>
<p>2. Binding Agreement. BY PURCHASING ANY PRODUCTS FROM US, YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE DEEMED TO HAVE READ, 
UNDERSTOOD AND AGREED TO ALL OF THE PROVISIONS OF THESE TERMS. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR AGREE TO ANYTHING IN THE 
IMMEDIATELY PRECEDING SENTENCE OR ANY OTHER PROVISION OF THESE TERMS, YOU SHOULD NOT PURCHASE ANY PRODUCTS FROM US.</p>
<p>3. Prices, Payment, and Delivery. All orders require a 50% deposit of estimated purchase price plus estimated costs 
(including sales tax and other charges) before work will commence and payment in full (including adjustments) is required 
before products will be shipped and title to the products transferred to you. Allprices may be corrected as a result of 
possible errors or omissions. You acknowledge that changes to designs may affect pricing and delivery schedules. 
Prices do notinclude freight, packing and handling charge, all of which are your sole responsibility. We are not 
responsible for delays in shipment beyond our control, including material shortages and labor or transit strikes, 
and will notify you in the event of such delays. All quoted delivery dates are estimates only. Products ready for 
delivery must be moved to your delivery location within ten (10) days after completion. Products which are not so 
moved may be transferred to a commercialwarehouse or storage facility at our sole discretion, and you will be liable 
for all costs and expenses incurred thereby, e.g., moving and storage fees and insurance. If payment for the products 
and related costs are not paid in full within sixty (60) days, we may, at our sole discretion, retain the products and the 
deposit as liquidated damages. You agree to pay all costs we incur in collecting unpaid accounts, including, 
but not limited to, collection agency fees and attorneys" fees.</p>
<p>4. Changes, Cancellations, and Returns. 
We will not accept changes, cancellations, or returns to an order without our prior written permission. In the event we do accept 
a cancellation or return, you agree to pay a 25% re-stocking charge. Any changes to an order, if accepted by us, are subject to
 a minimum $200.00 (two hundred dollar) fee. Custom or special order merchandise is not subject to cancellation or return.</p>
<p>5. Customer Claims and Risk of Loss. You shall bear all risk of loss or damage occurring while the merchandise is in transit or storage. 
It is recommended that you inspect all merchandise immediately upon delivery. If loss or damage is found, it is your responsibility
 to file any necessary freight claims with their carrier or storage facility.</p>
<p>6. Installation. You assume all responsibility for proper installation of the merchandise. We shall not be responsible for damage 
to the merchandise or to the location in which it is displayed and/or used. </p>
<p>7.WARRANTIES; DISCLAIMERS; LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. (a) WARRANTY DISCLAIMER. ALL PRODUCTS ARE SOLD "AS IS" AND ON AN "AS AVAILABLE" 
BASIS. FOR ALL PRODUCTS, WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, RELATED TO PRODUCTS, 
INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY ANY WARRANTY OFTITLE, ACCURACY, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR USE, WARRANTY 
OF NON-INFRINGEMENT, TITLE, QUIET ENJOYMENT OR WARRANTY RELATING TO THIRD PARTY SERVICES. You expressly waive any claim that you may
 have against us or our Affiliates based on any product liability or alleged infringement of any patent, copyright, trade secret or 
 other intellectual property rights with respect to any product and also waive any right toindemnification from us or our Affiliates 
 against claims made against you by a third party. You acknowledge that our employees are not authorized to make any representation 
 or warranty that is not in this Agreement. We do not warrant against fading and oxidizing, variations in tone, color, character, and
 texture ofwood and iron finishes, color variations in fabric dye lots or paint, fabric shrinking or stretching, deterioration of 
 dried plants used in artwork, or other normaldeterioration of elements used in our products. Our merchandise is not intended for 
 outdoor use, except where specifically noted. All of our accessories are fordecorated purposes only.(b) LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. 
 TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NONE OF US,OUR AFFILIATES, NOR ANY OF THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, 
 SHAREHOLDERS, MEMBERS, PARTNERS, EMPLOYEES, OR AGENTS SHALL BE LIABLE FOR PUNITIVE, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY, 
 INDIRECT, OR SPECIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, REVENUES, BUSINESS, USE, OR OTHER INTANGIBLES),WHETHER
 OR NOT SUCH DAMAGES WERE FORESEEABLE, WHETHER WE HAD BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OR LIKELIHOOD OF SUCH DAMAGES, OR FOR 
 ANY OTHER REASON.(c) MAXIMUM LIABILITY. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, OUR TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY 
 DAMAGES (REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OF ACTION, WHETHER CONTRACT, WARRANTY, TORT, PRODUCT LIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE) SHALL NOT EXCEED 
 IN THE AGGREGATE THE AMOUNT ACTUALLY PAID BY YOU TO US FOR THE PRODUCT GIVING RISE TO THE CLAIM.(d) INDEMNIFICATION. YOU AGREE 
 TO DEFEND AND INDEMNIFY US FROM AND AGAINST ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, DAMAGES, COSTS, AND EXPENSES, INCLUDING ATTORNEYS" FEES, ARISING 
 OUT OF OR RELATED TO YOUR US OF PRODUCTS.</p>
 <p>8. Governing Law and Jurisdiction. These Terms are governed by the laws of the State of
 California, United States, without regard to its choice of law principles. Subject to Paragraph 10 below, you consent to the jurisdiction 
 and venue of the state courts in Los Angeles County, California, and the federal courts in the Central District of California for all 
 disputes arising out of your purchase of the products.</p>
 <p>9. Arbitration.(a) YOU AGREE THAT THE SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE FORUM AND REMEDY FOR ANY 
 AND ALL DISPUTES AND CLAIMS RELATING IN ANY WAY TO OR ARISING OUT OF THESE TERMS OR ANY PRODUCTS SHALL BE FINAL AND BINDING ARBITRATION, 
 except that no dispute or claim relating to any transaction you enter into with a third party may be arbitrated.(b) The 
 arbitration shall be administered by JAMS pursuant to its Streamlined Arbitration Rules and Procedures (the "JAMS Rules.")
 Judgment on the award may be entered in any court having jurisdiction. The arbitration shall be held in Los Angeles, California. 
 Costs andfees for such arbitration shall be determined allocated in accordance with such JAMS Rules. If such costs are determined
 to be excessive in a consumer dispute, we will be responsible for paying all arbitration fees and arbitrator compensation in excess 
 of what is deemed reasonable. The arbitrator"s award shall be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent 
 jurisdiction.(c) TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NO ARBITRATION OR CLAIM UNDER THESE TERMS OF USE SHALL BE JOINED
 TO ANY OTHER ARBITRATION OR CLAIM AND NO CLASS ARBITRATION PROCEEDINGS SHALL BE PERMITTED. IN NO EVENT SHALL ANY CLAIM, ACTION OR 
 PROCEEDING BY YOU AGAINST OR INVOLVING US BE INSTITUTED MORE THAN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER YOUR CLAIM FIRST ACCRUED OR YOU FIRSTBECAME AWARE 
 OR REASONABLY SHOULD HAVE BECOME AWARE OF ANY SUCH CLAIM.</p>
 <p>10. Complete Agreement. This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between you and us with respect to the subject matter 
 contained herein. To the extent any of the provisions contained in our Privacy Policy and/or Terms of Use (available at www.dennisandleen.com 
 and/or www.formationsusa.com) would apply, such provisions are fully incorporated herein by this reference.</p>
        </div>
      </template>
</odoo>